<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paradise City Festival 2020</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Paradise City Festival 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 14:59:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First 20 names revealed !</title>
      <link>/news/the-first-20-names-revealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 14:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/the-first-20-names-revealed/</guid>
      <description>Here are the first 20 names of Paradise City festival 2020!
This is the first grasp of a total of 85 acts.
For us, it represents an eclectic mix of original artists and heavyweights that will perform at Paradise City 2020.
It&amp;rsquo;s just the beginning…
Other names will follow soon until the kick-off of the festival. The 6th edition will take place on 26, 27 and 28 June in Steenokkerzeel. You can already get your tickets here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ticket sale has started</title>
      <link>/news/ticket-sale-has-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/ticket-sale-has-started/</guid>
      <description>Dear citizens, Ticket sale for our 6th edition has started on Wednesday February 5th. The tickets with a Green Card discount are now accessible. Watch out as there’s a very limited amount of tickets available in Wave 1 of Green Card tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping</title>
      <link>/camping2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 13:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/camping2/</guid>
      <description>For campers, Paradise City is more than just a music festival, it is also a camping experience. Along with a rising sunshine and star-lit night skies, the intimate setting welcomes a fantastic crowd of music lovers.
We all know there’s nothing better than having a refreshing (hot) shower followed by a good coffee and a delicious breakfast, while listening to that guy who was playing piano – remember last year? – or maybe you were the one that woke up, unlocked his sweet little tent and saw his best mates already drinking an opened Carapils can… You took a sip too, kicking off the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Love, One Planet</title>
      <link>/news/1-love-1-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/1-love-1-planet/</guid>
      <description>You know we’ve been working hard since the launch of Paradise City on making it a green event. Sustainability and our ecological impact have always been at the core of Paradise City DNA. It has always demanded a lot of sweat and tears from our team, volunteers and suppliers. Goal achieved this year as we’ve been elected as 1 of the 6 greenest festivals in the world by A Greener Festival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green</title>
      <link>/news/green/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/green/</guid>
      <description>Global emissions keep beating records every year. The environmental crisis dawning upon us means that we all need to adapt fast and efficiently. The music industry needs to focus on this topic too. Since day one, sustainability sits at the core of Paradise City’s DNA. It implies taking into consideration various aspects regarding its organisation and its process. Paradise City is a meat-free and a no-single-use plastic festival. We not only recycle but we re-use everything we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping at Paradise City</title>
      <link>/news/camping-at-paradise-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/camping-at-paradise-city/</guid>
      <description>For campers, Paradise City is more than a music festival, it is also a camping experience. Along with a rising sunshine and star-lit night skies, the intimate setting welcomes a fantastic crowd of music lovers.
Our camping will be your personal chill-out area in the midst of festival insanity. There are different options to stay onsite:
 You can bring your own tent and camping equipment by buying a 3 days-ticket + camping or by buying a basic ticket for the camping for 35€.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/abstrkt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/abstrkt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/2manydjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/2manydjs/</guid>
      <description>The presence of the Belgian duo 2manydjs will be unmissable. The two brothers are what we can call legends - through their influence, their Deewee label and their other project Soulwax. We are more than delighted to welcome this duo for the second time, who represents the Belgian electronic music so well on the international scene. A very particular energy will set the Abstrkt Stage to close the festival on Sunday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/acid-pauli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/acid-pauli/</guid>
      <description>Over the last 20 years Martin Gretschmann has been exploring new fields of music off the mainstream paths: psychedelic, adventurous and full of musicality. With his solo project Acid Pauli he created several records, remixes and podcast in the last couple of years. Furthermore he took part in the unique project - The Golden Machine - a specifically developed electronic device which over the course of a whole year continuously produced music for a radio play, based on - Infinite Jest- by David Foster Wallace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/adam-port/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/adam-port/</guid>
      <description>Over the last years, Adam Port landed a string of much noticed releases on different labels, be it on Keinemusik, his Berlin-based label-mainstay and collective. And instead of doing the obvious, getting a management, meeting demands, playing those big stages, delivering the hits, Adam did what felt best for him. Maintaining artistic integrity, releasing records that reflect where his love for music is at in one moment, not knowing where it might be on the very next release, and keeping DJ-sets not only interesting for a crowd, but also himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/adi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/adi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/adriatique/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/adriatique/</guid>
      <description>After getting to know each other in Zürich in 2008, Adrian Shala &amp;amp; Adrian Schweizer became inseparable, not just as friends, but also as artists. The two men carved out a career as one of the most consistently delivering DJ/producer duos in the house and techno scene: Adriatique. Their respective preference for studio work and performance means that both aspects are equally well covered. Their performances as well as their productions are long, meditative, relentlessly building affairs, ever challenging the listener with subtle twists interrupting their hypnotic groove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/alia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/alia/</guid>
      <description>Driven by an intense love for electronic music in all its shapes, AliA is without a doubt one of the most promising deejays from Belgium. Being only 20 years old, she has a surprisingly thorough knowledge of club music and a mixing technique many envy. At this point in her early carreer AliA is already heavily supported by selectors Mr. Scruff, Carista and Lefto. Catch her on the Play Label Records Stage on Saturday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/ame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/ame/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/andras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/andras/</guid>
      <description>Andras is the stage name of Andrew Wilson (1988), an Australian musician who’s earned acclaim for his unpredictable take on dance music. His soft focused abstractions cut a broad path through ‘90s underground house, soundtrack and ambient music. His work is loosely based around drum machine rhythms and soft synthesis; smoothing over nature-machine and industrial-relaxation binaries and enjoying the slippage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/axel-boman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/axel-boman/</guid>
      <description>The last time Axel Boman had his biography written for him, he had just graduated from the Red Bull Music Academy, released his Purple Drank EP on DJ Koze’s Pampa label and was looking forward to releases on Permanent Vacation, Moodmusic and Hypercolour. The future looked promising. This rise in popularity could be down to his dashing good looks or smiley personality. But it could be down to his highly esteemed label, Studio Barnhus (he co-runs with Kornél Kovács and Pedrodollar) which has been responsible for presenting the most exciting house music around today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/ben-ufo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/ben-ufo/</guid>
      <description>Over the past five years, Ben UFO has acquired a deserved reputation as one of contemporary dance music’s most daring and wide-ranging selectors, with his keen ear and razor-sharp technical abilities enabling him to cut between eras, lineages and mixing styles with dazzling ease and fluidity. His roots lie in UK rave culture - yet his selections cast the net wider, drawing new mutations of this culture into the orbit of house, techno and other global dancefloor sounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/ceephax-acid-crew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/ceephax-acid-crew/</guid>
      <description>Dance producers nowadays are inclined to go on stage with a laptop under their arm and then stare at the screen. Not Andy Jenkinson, alias Ceephax Acid Crew. Ceephax drags his studio to every performance, puts a stack of drum computers and synths on stage and every track is performed live. While he scatters his acid over the audience, he also wants to have a conversation with them. Fuck Laptops! This is the real shit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/cellini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/cellini/</guid>
      <description>Cellini, as he is called, wields an extreme wide array of powerful sounds, sometimes deep and emotional, yet sometimes powerful and ecstatic. A harmonic blend between wandering sounds and kicking drums is the receipt of Cellini’s productions. He will take you on a journey through the deepest parts of the techno spectrum and translates infinite depth into audible sounds. The lines between physical and mental, tangible and supernatural, human and music got blurred while he’s on a stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/charlotte-adigery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/charlotte-adigery/</guid>
      <description>Having been taught the ropes by her mother, from rhythm over musicality to a sense of humour and not taking herself too seriously, Charlotte Adigéry got into music from an early age. Through mutual friends (after all Belgium is a tiny country) she was asked by the Soulwax brothers to lip-sync a song of theirs for the &amp;lsquo;Belgica&amp;rsquo; soundtrack they were producing at the time. As soon as they heard her voice, the acting job quickly turned into a studio session&amp;hellip; and another&amp;hellip; and another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/courtesy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/courtesy/</guid>
      <description>Najaaraq Vestbirk, aka Courtesy, is a DJ and label owner from Denmark. Pursuing and finding rare success solely as a DJ means she’s invested fully in her craft. Endless hours digging in the more overlooked sections of the world’s record shops while championing the newest music coming out of her Copenhagen hometown has resulted in a unique and thrilling sound. Her sets are as much for the head as they are the body – a place where fast, streamlined stompers sit alongside whip-crack electro and churning, wrongspeed EBM – held together by a common thread of smart and emotive melody.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/dan-shake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/dan-shake/</guid>
      <description>If you’re going to pick a name like Dan Shake, you better have the goods to back it up. His love of groove – ranging from sparky acid to Brazilian samba, itchy funk to heavyweight house – fuels his drive to make those around him dance as keenly as he does. At a party, Dan Shake isn’t just loaded with peak time weapons: he is one. As his sound has evolved and his reputation as a killer DJ has grown, Shake’s love of connecting to the dancers in front of him has remained, well, unshakable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/dj-dustin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/dj-dustin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/dwig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/dwig/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/edward/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/edward/</guid>
      <description>Gilles Aiken, the Berlin DJ better known as Edward, makes shadowy club tracks with a surrealistic edge. Much of Edward his music is based on samples and edits, which he playfully manipulates into a blend of psychedelic and ambient house. Catch him on Sunday at the Giegling stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/eli-verveine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/eli-verveine/</guid>
      <description>For as long as Eli Verveine has been mixing records she has strived for the perfect groove and flow, the one that keeps you moving and the dancefloor rocking. After two decades, thousands of satisfied dancers will happily testify to her uncanny knack of finding and working that groove. Since honing her skills over years warming up the dancefloor, she has developed into a superlative peak-time DJ who also still loves to play extended after-hours sets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/elli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/elli/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/fedele/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/fedele/</guid>
      <description>Originally from Bari, Italy, Fedele Ladisa is part of the emerging wave of DJ producers which are eager to explore new territories of electronic music and one of the three minds behind the already acclaimed Italian Agents of Time.
In 2006 he entered the universe of DJing and started performing in different clubs around the world. His penchant for electronic music led him to master the universe of synthesizer techniques and drum machines and to start creating his own productions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/gidge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/gidge/</guid>
      <description>Gidge is a duo consisting of Jonatan Nilsson and Ludvig Stolterman from Umeå, a city in the north of Sweden. Jonatan and Ludvig met in school and had a mutual interest for electronic music. After taking a sound production class, they started producing music. Using the woods and widths of the North as their main source of inspiration, the music of Gidge sounds like a mixture of electronic music and organic elements, such as wooden and stone percussions that the duo recorded in the forests outside of Umeå.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/hunee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/hunee/</guid>
      <description>Every DJ would like to think themselves a real musical connoisseur, but Hunee really is - it’s not him that says so, but pretty much anyone else whenever the man born Hun Choi pops up in conversation. His DJ sets have of course taken him all over the world but they take listeners much further. As likely to draw for a classic house record as he is a disco curveball, a boogie delight or mixing an African bomb into a techno record, each selection he makes is a thing of true passion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/hvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/hvl/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/innellea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/innellea/</guid>
      <description>Innellea – a neologism, created in reference to the musical reinvention of the artist is from Munich. Not restrained or bound by conventions, Innellea’s visions and impressions are visibly transferred into his music. He’s creating his personal journey to reach an undefined destination, without a lack of impetus. Influenced by melodic trends in the electronic music, he found his way to combine it with the roots of techno in a very creative way and came up with his own abstract sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/islandman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/islandman/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/jaguar-jaguar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/jaguar-jaguar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/kalabrese-rumpelorchester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/kalabrese-rumpelorchester/</guid>
      <description>Kalabrese is one of the more glittering characters in Zurich’s music scene and mingling at the frontline as DJ, producer and as co-owner of the legendary club Zukunft. Through his very own style as a producer, Sacha Winkler caused a stir outside of Switzerland. Radio stations like KCRW in America or Sonica Ibiza played regularly times songs of the independent dancer album. Spotify playlists and over 200k-regular members helped also to spread Kalabreses non-perfect dance groove in the last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/kelly-lee-owens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/kelly-lee-owens/</guid>
      <description>Kelly Lee Owens&amp;rsquo; masterful second album “Inner Song” finds the convention-blurring techno producer and singer/songwriter diving deep into her own psyche-excoriating the struggles she&amp;rsquo;s faced over the last several years and exploring personal pain while embracing the beauty of the natural world. It&amp;rsquo;s a leap in artistry from a musician who burst forth on the scene with a confident, rich sound, and is endlessly enticing when it comes to what Owens is capable of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/kerri-chandler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/kerri-chandler/</guid>
      <description>No one unites a club like Kerri Chandler. No one’s kick kicks harder. No one’s keys carry more emotion. No crowd reacts with more energy than when the New Jersey great is behind the decks. His life-long obsession with sound makes him famously meticulous about the setups of the clubs he plays, and that always results in electrifying sets of soulful, authentic, positive house music. Rather than mechanical grooves, he lays down spiritual rhythms that permeate every part of your body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/kink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/kink/</guid>
      <description>KiNK has become one of house music’s most in demand producers and remixers: his tracks easily stand out in any club night and they are second to none in the most competitive environment electronic music has ever seen. His abilities in finding the ‘sweet spot’ of new machines and even of sounds considered ‘classic’ and to reshape them into totally different beasts would be totally enough to justify the phenomenon. KiNK’s music is unifying in the best possible way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/kruder-dorfmeister/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/kruder-dorfmeister/</guid>
      <description>Kruder &amp;amp; Dorfmeister started making music together in the early 1990s. At the time, Vienna was a metropolis of the aspiring techno movement. But the two gentlemen rather followed the tradition of the continental cosmic “dancefloor” of the 1980s. K&amp;amp;D always enjoyed not following advice and abandoned all of the enticing major offers. Instead, they provided musician friends with distribution on their G-Stone label, hung out in the studio and put together follow-up projects, like Dorfmeister &amp;amp; Huber’s Tosca or Kruder’s Peace Orchestra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/laurence-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/laurence-guy/</guid>
      <description>DJ, Producer and purveyor of quality house music, UK artist Laurence Guy has amassed a collection of loyal listeners and tastemakers. From his album on Church Records in 2017 through to his Mule Musiq EP and 2019 mini-album on Studio Barnhus, Guy’s mature and seasoned releases have been consistently acclaimed whilst stylistically diverse. A restless digger, Laurence can also be found rummaging through the dusty crates of his local record shops, informing the sound of his refined DJ sets, edits label Accidental Pieces and Rinse FM residency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/lawrence/</guid>
      <description>There is a remarkable elegance to the way Lawrence found his space as an artist in the universe of subtle House and deep Techno. Lawrence produces, djs and on rare occasions plays live. Doing this for almost two decades, he&amp;rsquo;s released a considerable number of records on his co-owned labels Dial and Smallville along with releases on Mule Musiq, Pampa, Ghostly International and others. His last album “Illusion” (Dial, 2018) is dedicated to the passionate underground scene with its old and new originators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/leafar-legov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/leafar-legov/</guid>
      <description>As a solo artist, he explores the cinematic and experimental edges of ambient, house and techno.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/levon-vincent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/levon-vincent/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to house music there’s been something of a renaissance in New York City this past decade and one of its main advocates is Levon Vincent. As a clubgoer, he cut his teeth during the pre-Giuliani New York heyday, where a vibrant scene was helping to push the elegant sound that would become known as NY house forward – and Levon witnessed it all first-hand. Levon joined a long, proud lineage of fringe arts based around New York’s downtown culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/lola-haro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/lola-haro/</guid>
      <description>Lola Haro is all about crazy bangers. Her love and passion for music and her authentic approach have been refreshing and gave her a lot of recognition on the Belgian club scene. In only 12 months’ time, she earned a residency at Paradise City Festival and Kiosk Radio, got her first Boiler Room under her belt, shared the DJ booth with countless highly respected international selectors and was awarded as “Most Promising artist of 2019” by Red Bull Elektropedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/mapache/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/mapache/</guid>
      <description>Map.ache is a DJ and producer from Leipzig, Germany. He is also one half of the DJ duo Manamana as well as co-founder of the record label KANN. To add more strings to his bow, Map.ache is a Giegling affiliate and a much sought after remixer. In Leipzig, he has been a big huge contributor to the local scene, formerly being the booker of Leipzig Institution Conne Island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/max-cooper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/max-cooper/</guid>
      <description>Few have been so successful in interrogating and furthering the intersection between electronic music, visual art, technology and science in the past decade as Max Cooper. Whether a walk-through light installation, ground-breaking use of 4D sound, or club-ready techno releases, Cooper’s output is a classic case of electronic exploration that makes use of available technology while referencing that which came before it and does so in a human way. What now drives the Belfast-born artist as he set out on a fresh cycle for his fourth studio album Yearning for the Infinite was to create a lasting human impression through technology and machinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/mezerg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/mezerg/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/mezigue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/mezigue/</guid>
      <description>It has been several years now that ​Mézigue has been inviting himself into the lives of those who wanted to see him. Adept of Mézigue himself, he draws his inspiration from French slang, concrete, nature and the emptiness that constitutes everything. Mézigue does not like talking about Mézigue, he’s the one who wrote this biography and he prefers to keep it confidential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/molly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/molly/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/move-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/move-d/</guid>
      <description>Move D, aka David Moufang, is one of the modern electronic music most beloved souls with a long and varied musical history with roots in the 60s and 70s jazz, psychedelic, rock, soul and early electronica. Making his first appearance on vinyl as part of a school bands competition in 1983, it was only another four years before he started toying with the medium as a DJ, playing funk, soul, hip-hop, and proto-house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/mr-g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/mr-g/</guid>
      <description>The term &amp;lsquo;legend&amp;rsquo; is often banded around willy nilly in the dance music realm, but Mr. G, aka Colin McBean, is one of the few who can rightfully lay claim to this accolade. Having been in the game for around 2 decades now, Mr. G is widely considered to be one of the most under-rated artists about - with only true music fans appreciating his vast contribution to dance music. Having achieved great acclaim for releases on labels such as Defected, Duty Free, The End and Skint/Loaded, and remixing a wide range of artists, he also received much attention for his releases/remixes out of Detroit on Moods ‘n’ Grooves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/nico-morano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/nico-morano/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the years the sound of Nico Morano has developed into one of the most sophisticated ones in Belgium. His blend of deep, melodic house with a strong emotional touch has been picked up by many others. Nico is all about creating an intangible mood in every way he can. And out of this unique quality in combination with his urge for pushing boundaries and reaching like-minded people, the party concept of More Morano arose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/nosedrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/nosedrip/</guid>
      <description>In the space of just a few years, Ostend-based Nosedrip, real name Ziggy Devriendt, has gone from somewhat of a now-you-see-me-now-you-don’t presence on the fringe electronic scene to a firm fixture on Belgium’s burgeoning leftfield landscape, albeit one that revels in his outsider status, thanks to a unique mixture of oddball playlists and distinctive aesthetics, his staggering Mixcloud following, an NTS show and, more recently, a label imprint with considerable, if not slightly tongue -in-cheek, ambitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/orla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/orla/</guid>
      <description>Or:la first burst onto the production scene in 2016 after her debut release, &amp;lsquo;UK Lonely&amp;rsquo; on Hotflush Recordings. What separates Or:la from many other young DJ&amp;rsquo;s at the moment is a vast knowledge of various genres and tempos. Her success as a dynamic producer and genre-spanning selector has seen her gain a residency at the Warehouse Project in Manchester, a bimonthly show on NTS Radio and she has been rewarded by DJ Mag as ‘Breakthrough DJ of the year’ in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/paquita-gordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/paquita-gordon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/red-d-lefto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/red-d-lefto/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/ry-x-frank-wiedemann-howling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/ry-x-frank-wiedemann-howling/</guid>
      <description>Though they come from quite opposite ends of the spectrum, there’s a tangible sense of understanding and appreciation between singer/producer/cult artist Ry X and producer/live electronic artist/label owner Frank Wiedemann. Ry X and Frank’s musical influences are remarkably aligned, as are their creative mindsets. Both artists’ backgrounds meld together to create productions that transcend categorization: subtle yet deeply moving songs that glisten with divine instrumentation and percussion. They often use the word “magic” when describing their productions, live performances and the project as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/sam/</guid>
      <description>The S.A.M. sound has been characterized as cosmic, trippy, spiritual, psychedelic, peaceful, and groovy. It’s the combination of these attributes with the playfully danceable beats and smiling performances that has brought S.A.M. to be one of the most interesting underground acts of today. Samuel Andre Madsen grew up in a religious family in the countryside of Denmark, helping out in church playing the drums and bass guitar. Later when he moved to Copenhagen, he met electronic music, and started producing and DJ’ing while studying Theology at the University and working as a church keeper on the side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/schatrax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/schatrax/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/susobrino/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/susobrino/</guid>
      <description>Field Recordings, percussion, electronic spice and acoustic instruments. These are the ingredients chosen to create the perfect Belgian Bolivian. His didactic study for percussion and rhythm was the focus of his new album “La Hoja de Eucalipto” that brings alive a more active and aggressive part of Susobrino. The Bolivian Indiana Jones presented his first serene EP “Mapajo” in 2018. An EP fully made of his field recording trip to Bolivia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/trikk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/trikk/</guid>
      <description>One of Porto’s finest exports, Trikk was praised as a young talent and embraced by so many as new star to look out for. After releasing on labels such ManMakeMusic and Lossless and remixes for Hotflush Recordings, Pets Recordings and more, nothing was left to prove. As a personal challenge, he moved to London where he now spends his days producing music and djing. Trikk explores mainly house aesthetics in complex tracks, wisely composed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/artist/vril/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist/vril/</guid>
      <description>Seemingly out of nothing, through dust and with no bang, Vril appeared on the scene. His music made such beautiful noise that it instantly found his place on Marcel Dettmann’s selection for his Conducted cd and on Ostgut’s release schedule. His sound is a search for the evergoing movement, exploring a never stopping energy. Once he catches you in his groove it will shine so bright you won’t be able to escape it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstrkt</title>
      <link>/stages/abstrakt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stages/abstrakt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beste inwoners van Steenokkerzeel</title>
      <link>/steenokkerzeel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/steenokkerzeel/</guid>
      <description>Op 26, 27 en 28 Juni is Steenokkerzeel opnieuw het mooie decor van Paradise City Festival, het groenste festival van het land. Paradise City zou niet hetzelfde zijn zonder jullie talrijke opkomst. En vooral op vrijdag willen we er een heus buurtfeest van maken, met extra voordelen voor alle inwoners van Steenokkerzeel. Zoals vorig jaar wordt Vrijdag een volwaardige festivaldag: de deuren gaan open om 14u, er zijn 4 stages met grote namen die we binnenkort gaan aankondigen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping</title>
      <link>/camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/camping/</guid>
      <description>For campers, Paradise City is more than just a music festival, it is also a camping experience. Along with a rising sunshine and star-lit night skies, the intimate setting welcomes a fantastic crowd of music lovers. We all know there’s nothing better than having a refreshing (hot) shower followed by a good coffee and a delicious breakfast, while listening to that guy who was playing piano – remember last year? – or maybe you were the one that woke up, unlocked his sweet little tent and saw his best mates already drinking an opened Carapils can… You took a sip too, kicking off the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discount for students</title>
      <link>/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/students/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a student? Fill the form below &amp;amp; get a discount! Student life can be expensive so as a student we are offering you a discount on Friday July 5 tickets! Join us from 14:00 to 01:00 for only 39€ instead of 59€. To benefit from this discount you need to be a student. We will validate this with your email address from your school/university. Please fill in the following info and we’ll send you a discount code with 48 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Involved</title>
      <link>/get-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/get-involved/</guid>
      <description>Paradise City wasn’t built by itself. It’s the result of hard work by countless volunteers months before the due date, during and even after the festival. Together, we envision what a city of the future can look like with people working hand in hand to create something truly special.
For every citizen on the dancefloor having the time of his life, there’s someone making it happen behind the curtains. As a volunteer, you are super precious to us, as you’re on site and you directly represent the festival to our festivalgoers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here is our food trucks &amp; restaurants selection !</title>
      <link>/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/food/</guid>
      <description>Here is the list we&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line-Up</title>
      <link>/lineup2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lineup2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line-Up</title>
      <link>/lineupz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lineupz/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical - FAQ</title>
      <link>/practical/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/practical/</guid>
      <description>Looking for info about the festival, tickets, access? You&amp;rsquo;re at the right place!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Respect the nature, respect the castle</title>
      <link>/green/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/green/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Line-Up</title>
      <link>/lineup2/saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lineup2/saturday/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you for your submission.</title>
      <link>/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>We will get back to you as soon as possible ! ← Back to homepage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tickets</title>
      <link>/tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tickets/</guid>
      <description>Green card owner or looking for the early access tickets ?
green card shopearly bird shop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timetable</title>
      <link>/timetable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/timetable/</guid>
      <description>14:00 14:30 15:00 15:30 16:00 16:30 17:00 17:30 18:00 18:30 19:00 19:30 20:00 20:30 21:00 21:30 22:00 22:30 23:00 00:00 00:30 01:00      Under My Garage  19:00 - 21:00 Ben UFO     21:00 - 23:00 Nosedrip     17:00 - 19:00 Paquita Gordon       Giegling   17:00 - 19:00 DJ Dustin    16:00 - 17:00 Dwig Live    14:00 - 16:00 Elli    19:00 - 20:00 Lawrence Live    22:00 - 23:00 Map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timetable</title>
      <link>/timetable/friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/timetable/friday/</guid>
      <description>14:00 14:30 15:00 15:30 16:00 16:30 17:00 17:30 18:00 18:30 19:00 19:30 20:00 20:30 21:00 21:30 22:00 22:30 23:00 00:00 00:30 01:00      Love    Contrair      Under My Garge      TBA       -- 14:00 14:30 15:00 15:30 16:00 16:30 17:00 17:30 18:00 18:30 19:00 19:30 20:00 20:30 21:00 21:30 22:00 22:30 23:00 00:00 00:30 01:00      Under My Garage  19:00 - 21:00 Ben UFO     21:00 - 23:00 Nosedrip     17:00 - 19:00 Paquita Gordon       Giegling   17:00 - 19:00 DJ Dustin    16:00 - 17:00 Dwig Live    14:00 - 16:00 Elli    19:00 - 20:00 Lawrence Live    22:00 - 23:00 Map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timetable</title>
      <link>/timetable/saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/timetable/saturday/</guid>
      <description>11:00 11:30 12:00 12:30 13:00 13:30 14:00 14:30 15:00 15:30 16:00 16:30 17:00 17:30 18:00 18:30 19:00 19:30 20:00 20:30 21:00 21:30 22:00 22:30 23:00 00:00 00:30 01:00      Love  21:00 - 23:00 Adriatique    19:00 - 21:00 Axel Boman    15:45 - 17:15 Cellini    13:00 - 14:15 Innellea Live    17:15 - 19:00 Lola Haro      Giegling   17:00 - 18:00 HVL Live    18:00 - 20:00 Levon Vincent    20:00 - 21:00 VRIL Live      Paradise City Live    13:40 - 14:50 Gidge Live    16:30 - 17:30 Islandman    18:30 - 19:30 Kelly Lee Owens Live    12:30 - 13:40 Laurence Guy Live    19:40 - 21:10 Max Cooper Live    17:30 - 18:30 Mezerg    21:10 - 23:00 S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timetable</title>
      <link>/timetable/sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/timetable/sunday/</guid>
      <description>10:30 11:00 11:30 12:00 12:30 13:00 13:30 14:00 14:30 15:00 15:30 16:00 16:30 17:00 17:30 18:00 18:30 19:00 19:30 20:00 20:30 21:00 21:30 22:00 22:30 23:00        Abstrkt  19:00 - 21:00 2manydjs    18:00 - 19:00 Charlotte Adigéry    12:00 - 13:00 Jaguar Jaguar    13:00 - 15:00 Kruder &amp;amp; Dorfmeister      Giegling   10:30 - 13:00 Adi    18:00 - 20:00 Edward    13:00 - 16:00 Eli Verveine    20:00 - 21:00 Leafar Legov Live    16:00 - 18:00 Molly       Silo   13:30 - 15:00 Ceephax Acid Crew Live    15:00 - 17:00 Courtesy    18:00 - 21:00 Hunee    17:00 - 18:00 Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want to get in touch with us ?</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> Name
  Email
  Message
  Send →  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>