<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The writings on the walls on Paradise City Festival 2020</title>
    <link>/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The writings on the walls on Paradise City Festival 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 18:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ticket sale starts on February 15th at 4pm</title>
      <link>/news/ticket-sale-starts-on-february-15th-at-4pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/ticket-sale-starts-on-february-15th-at-4pm/</guid>
      <description>Dear citizens, Ticket sale for our 6th edition has started on Wednesday February 5th. Early Birds and tickets with a Green Card discount are now accessible. Watch out as there’s a very limited amount of tickets available in Wave 1 of Green Card tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become an Ambassador</title>
      <link>/news/ambassador/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 18:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/ambassador/</guid>
      <description>Become an official Paradise City ambassador and earn tickets and exclusive experiences by selling tickets to Paradise City Festival 2020!
Rewards to claim
 Friday ticket Saturday ticket Sunday ticket Weekend ticket Holiday ticket Camping ticket €40 Credit Weekend ticket for you and one of your friend  How does the program work?
You’ll earn points for every ticket that you sell to your friends. You can then use these points to redeem rewards in a shop within your ambassador dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping</title>
      <link>/news/camping-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 18:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/camping-1/</guid>
      <description>For campers, Paradise City is more than a music festival, it is also a camping experience. Along with a rising sunshine and star-lit night skies, the intimate setting welcomes a fantastic crowd of music lovers.
Our camping will be your personal chill-out area in the midst of festival insanity. There are different options to stay onsite:
 You can bring your own tent and camping equipment by buying a 3 days-ticket + camping or by buying a basic ticket for the camping for 35€.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Love, 1 Planet</title>
      <link>/news/1-love-1-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 18:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/1-love-1-planet/</guid>
      <description>You know we’ve been working hard since the launch of Paradise City on making it a green event. Sustainability and our ecological impact have always been at the core of Paradise City DNA. It has always demanded a lot of sweat and tears from our team, volunteers and suppliers. Goal achieved this year as we’ve been elected as 1 of the 6 greenest festivals in the world by A Greener Festival.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>