<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The writings on the walls on Paradise City Festival 2020</title>
    <link>/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The writings on the walls on Paradise City Festival 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>/news/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/test/</guid>
      <description>Test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical information</title>
      <link>/news/practical-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 21:58:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/practical-information/</guid>
      <description>Dear Citizens, Paradise City is just around the corner, time to share some practical information about the festival&amp;hellip;
OPENING HOURS Friday : 14:00 - 01:00
Saturday : 12:00 - 01:00
Sunday : 12:00 - 23:00
TOP UP YOUR CREDITS IN ADVANCE As you probably know we are a cashless festival, that means you will get a wristband with a chip on it.
Don’t forget to charge your wristband in advance by creating your personal account on Playpass and avoid queuing at Paradise City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday &amp; Saturday tickets SOLD OUT!</title>
      <link>/news/holiday-saturday-tickets-sold-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:24:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/holiday-saturday-tickets-sold-out/</guid>
      <description>Holiday &amp;amp; Saturday Tickets are completely sold out!
No worries we still have some Combi Tickets left if you want to join us for the whole weekend.
Friday Tickets (with Mind Against, Polo &amp;amp; Pan, John Talabot, Gerd Janson &amp;amp; more) and Sunday Tickets (with Dixon, Dj Koze, Todd Terje, 2manydjs &amp;amp; more) are still available at the moment.
Tickets</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put credits in your wristband with Payconiq by Bancontact</title>
      <link>/news/download-the-payconiq-app-and-get-some-major-advantages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 20:24:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/download-the-payconiq-app-and-get-some-major-advantages/</guid>
      <description>As you probably know we are a cashless festival, that means you will get a wristband with a chip on it.On this chip you’ll have to load up money to be able to buy drinks and food.
For a seamless Paradise City experience you should consider putting credits on your personal account before the festival weekend.
Just as last year we are partnering up with Payconiq by Bancontact, they will offer you 2 major advantages!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brussels: Important Transport Information</title>
      <link>/news/brussels-important-transport-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 17:05:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/brussels-important-transport-information/</guid>
      <description>With the Tour de France happening during the weekend of 6 &amp;amp; 7 July in Brussels it won’t be easy to travel from Brussels to Paradise City. But we have arranged several options for you…
BY BUS Electric busses given by Brussels Airport will bring you from Roodebeek station to Paradise City. After the festival the bus shuttles will drop people at Central Station with a stop at Roodebeek for the ones who left their means of transport there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share a &#34;Taxi Verts&#34; and get a 15€ discount</title>
      <link>/news/share-a-taxi-verts-and-get-a-15-discount/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 23:30:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/share-a-taxi-verts-and-get-a-15-discount/</guid>
      <description>We partnered up with Taxis Verts, so you can easily order a taxi via their smartphone application. Share a taxi with friends and get 15 € discount on your order via the Taxis Verts’ app with promo code PARADISECITY.
- Activate your 15 € discount in 3 simple steps
- Download the Taxis Verts app in the App Store or Google Play
- Link a credit card to your account and enter your pick-up and drop-off address</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foodtrucks</title>
      <link>/news/foodtrucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 15:43:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/foodtrucks/</guid>
      <description>We believe that good music tastes even better when accompanied by good food! Our food trucks serve delicious food with minimum impact on the environment. Ingredients are seasonal and biological, served in compostable tablewear. The menus are mostly vegetarian, but there is also room for sustainably caught fish. What’s more, all these various food trucks are joining forces to source their ingredients locally.
Jean sur Mer
Jean Sur Mer is one of the pioneers on the Belgian Food Truck scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brasserie 2050 : The restaurant of the future</title>
      <link>/news/brasserie-2050-the-restaurant-of-the-future-comes-to-paradise-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 18:26:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/brasserie-2050-the-restaurant-of-the-future-comes-to-paradise-city/</guid>
      <description>Imagine a restaurant where you can taste the future. A future filled with healthy food for all. Well, here it is.
Taste the future The concept of Brasserie 2050 was created in 2018 by Rabobank, partnered with MOJO, The Food Line-up and Overtreders W. The bank’s mission: Growing a better world together. As Tom van Kuyk (Rabobank’s manager of brand experience and partnerships) puts it: in 2050 we’ll be 10 billion people on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise City App</title>
      <link>/news/paradise-city-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 17:25:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/paradise-city-app/</guid>
      <description>Download our app for iOS &amp;amp; Android! Get all the latest updates about the festival and personalize your timetable to avoid missing on any of your favorite artists.
Download it here:
iOS: bit.ly/iOSAPP19 Android: bit.ly/PlayAPP19</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New music label and first release “Greatest Hits” by DJ Oufti</title>
      <link>/news/paradise-city-festival-launches-new-label-and-releases-first-ep-greatest-hits-from-dj-oufti/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:29:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/paradise-city-festival-launches-new-label-and-releases-first-ep-greatest-hits-from-dj-oufti/</guid>
      <description>2 weeks ahead of the 5th edition of Paradise City Festival, we are launching our label “Paradise City Records”. The label is not really part of a big strategy, one night we were listening to some unreleased tracks from a friend and we stumbled on some great music. We decided that we had to release this music instead of letting it disappear on a hard drive. And that’s basically how the label idea started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free electric bus shuttles by Brussels Airport</title>
      <link>/news/free-electric-bus-shuttles-by-brussels-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:24:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/free-electric-bus-shuttles-by-brussels-airport/</guid>
      <description>Brussels Airport is a proud sponsor &amp;amp; sustainability partner of Paradise City and to help us reach our green ambitions, they will use 4 electric buses to transport visitors between the festival and Brussels/Vilvoorde during the 3 festival days. It is estimated that around 600 festival-goers will use this shuttle service every day.
The shuttles from Vilvoorde train station and to Brussels Airport train station are free and do not necessit a ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Culinary Curator at Paradise City 2019</title>
      <link>/news/seppe-nobels-as-new-culinary-curator-at-paradise-city-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 15:41:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/seppe-nobels-as-new-culinary-curator-at-paradise-city-2019/</guid>
      <description>Fine cuisine has always been one of the main pillars of Paradise City Festival. Since our first edition in 2015 where we had a no fast food policy to the 2016 edition where we decided to ban meat from the festival, we have always had a gastronomic experience with a prestigious chef at our Comfort zone.
Discover this year&amp;rsquo;s curator in the following video&amp;hellip;
 Culinary Curator This year we are planning big things with our new culinary curator Seppe Nobels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gastronomic experience by Seppe Nobels (Graanmarkt 13) </title>
      <link>/news/gastronomic-experience-by-seppe-nobels-graanmarkt-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 15:17:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/gastronomic-experience-by-seppe-nobels-graanmarkt-13/</guid>
      <description>Come and enjoy a gastronomic experience curated by Seppe Nobels and Graanmarkt 13 at our Comfort zone on the island. You can easily appreciate the sight of our main stage and on the Castle, while chilling on this exceptional environment.
The Comfort zone provides an easy-going and friendly atmosphere where you can keep up with your pace. The gastronomic experience is included in the Comfort ticket.
Take pleasure in the gastronomic experience, which is a 5-course meal with accompanying drinks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover our 5th anniversary line-up </title>
      <link>/news/discover-a-part-of-our-5th-anniversary-line-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 13:36:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/discover-a-part-of-our-5th-anniversary-line-up/</guid>
      <description>Discover the complete line-up for our fifth anniversary! While reading, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to put our Spotify playlist on.
 Paradise City’s purpose has always been to highlight the cozy side of electronic music. When you’re on the dance floor, something happens. A positive and particular energy emerges. Our job goes further than programming only headliners. At Paradise City, we really want to introduce new talents and this year, we still support the local scene with all its great Belgian artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giegling</title>
      <link>/news/giegling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 19:10:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/giegling/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating its 10th anniversary this year, Giegling will host a stage for 2 days at Paradise City. We are beyond excited about this. For those who know Giegling it needs no further introduction. For those who are not familiar with Giegling, they are known for their focus on the deeper realms of house and techno.
Finding their music can be tricky as they only release it on vinyl. But here&amp;rsquo;s a playlist for you to discover their beautiful sound&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BECOME AN AMBASSADOR</title>
      <link>/news/become-an-ambassador/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 11:40:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/become-an-ambassador/</guid>
      <description>Become an official Paradise City ambassador and earn tickets and exclusive experiences by selling tickets to Paradise City Festival 2019!
Rewards to claim
 Friday ticket Saturday ticket Sunday ticket Weekend ticket Holiday ticket Camping ticket €40 Credit Weekend ticket for you and 1 friend  How Does the Program Work?
You’ll earn points for every ticket that you sell to your friends. You can then use these points to redeem rewards in a shop within your ambassador dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbon Footprint </title>
      <link>/news/carbon-footprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 11:18:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/carbon-footprint/</guid>
      <description>Sustainability is in our festival’s DNA since day 1.
It implies taking into consideration various aspects regarding its organisation and its process, gathering many data in order to be sure to improve the festival&amp;rsquo;s ecological impact for each edition. And we are very proud to realize, year after year, that our strict policies are effective and that, thanks to our citizens, we are reducing our impact on the planet. This video shows how we achieve it and what are the steps that we should still implement to further reduce our inevitable CO2 consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ticket sale starts on February 12th at 16pm</title>
      <link>/news/ticket-sale-starts-on-february-12th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 18:15:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/ticket-sale-starts-on-february-12th/</guid>
      <description>Dear citizens,  Please mark you agenda’s on February 12th as ticket sale will start on that day! Early Birds and tickets with a Green Card discount will be available from then on. Watch out as there’s a very limited amount of tickets available in Wave 1 of Green Card tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th Anniversary Edition</title>
      <link>/news/5th-anniversary-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 16:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/5th-anniversary-edition/</guid>
      <description>2019 marks our 5th anniversary and our excitement is mounting to deliver the most special edition to date. The Paradise City recipe has been quite simple from the start in 2015: mix the best electronic music on offer with open minded people and a strong effort to minimize our ecological footprint. Meanwhile our intention has always been a dancefloor packed with energy, where people dance, live euphoric moments and connect with the artists and each-other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>