<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The writings on the wall on Paradise City Festival 2020</title>
    <link>/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The writings on the wall on Paradise City Festival 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 14:59:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First 20 names revealed !</title>
      <link>/news/the-first-20-names-revealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 14:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/the-first-20-names-revealed/</guid>
      <description>Here are the first 20 names of Paradise City festival 2020!
This is the first grasp of a total of 85 acts.
For us, it represents an eclectic mix of original artists and heavyweights that will perform at Paradise City 2020.
It&amp;rsquo;s just the beginning…
Other names will follow soon until the kick-off of the festival. The 6th edition will take place on 26, 27 and 28 June in Steenokkerzeel. You can already get your tickets here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ticket sale has started</title>
      <link>/news/ticket-sale-has-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/ticket-sale-has-started/</guid>
      <description>Dear citizens, Ticket sale for our 6th edition has started on Wednesday February 5th. The tickets with a Green Card discount are now accessible. Watch out as there’s a very limited amount of tickets available in Wave 1 of Green Card tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Love, One Planet</title>
      <link>/news/1-love-1-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/1-love-1-planet/</guid>
      <description>You know we’ve been working hard since the launch of Paradise City on making it a green event. Sustainability and our ecological impact have always been at the core of Paradise City DNA. It has always demanded a lot of sweat and tears from our team, volunteers and suppliers. Goal achieved this year as we’ve been elected as 1 of the 6 greenest festivals in the world by A Greener Festival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green</title>
      <link>/news/green/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/green/</guid>
      <description>Global emissions keep beating records every year. The environmental crisis dawning upon us means that we all need to adapt fast and efficiently. The music industry needs to focus on this topic too. Since day one, sustainability sits at the core of Paradise City’s DNA. It implies taking into consideration various aspects regarding its organisation and its process. Paradise City is a meat-free and a no-single-use plastic festival. We not only recycle but we re-use everything we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping at Paradise City</title>
      <link>/news/camping-at-paradise-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/camping-at-paradise-city/</guid>
      <description>For campers, Paradise City is more than a music festival, it is also a camping experience. Along with a rising sunshine and star-lit night skies, the intimate setting welcomes a fantastic crowd of music lovers.
Our camping will be your personal chill-out area in the midst of festival insanity. There are different options to stay onsite:
 You can bring your own tent and camping equipment by buying a 3 days-ticket + camping or by buying a basic ticket for the camping for 35€.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>